<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<resources cache="true" online="false">

	<entry key="DiagonalTrapContent">
		<lang key="de"><h1>Diagonal Trap</h1><div class="content">
    Die [DiagonalTrap] ist eine Taktik die darauf ausgerichtet ist einen Nutzen zu ziehen aus der 
    limitierten Beweglichkeit der [MovDiagonal] Einheiten, zum Beispiel: [Eagle], [Pretorian], 
    [Doomer] or [Interceptor]. 
    <p>
    Die [CombatUnits] mit [MovDiagonal] können steckenbleiben ohne jede Möglichkeit der Flucht wenn 
    sie feindliche [CombatUnits] auf allen Vierecken haben die ihnen zur Verfügung stehen.
    Eine Einheit kann nur frontal angreifen, deshalb sind sie komplett verwundbar.
    </p><p>
    Das folgende Beispiel zeigt eine [DiagonalTrap] an allen vier Ecken:

    <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap2.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example"/>

    And this example shows a [DiagonalTrap] on the extremity of the [GameBoard]:
    
    <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap1.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example"/>

  Du solltest sehr vorsichtig sein wenn du deine [CombatUnits] mit [MovDiagonal] zu den Extremitäten 
  des [GameBoard] bewegst. Sie verlieren nicht nur 50% Mobilität, sie werden auch viel anfälliger für 
  eine [DiagonalTrap].

  </p><h2>Wie bekämpft man eine Diagonal Falle?</h2>
  Der beste Weg diese Falle zu bekämpfen ist sie total zu vermeiden. Dennoch, wenn dein Gegner es 
  schafft die Falle anzuwenden, ist der einzige Fluchtweg andere [CombatUnits] zu benutzen um 
  diejenigen die die Falle aufstellen zu zerstören.
    </div></lang>
		<lang key="en"><h1>Diagonal Trap</h1><div class="content">
    The [DiagonalTrap] is a tactic that aims to take advantage of the movement limitations of the
    [MovDiagonal] units, for example: [Eagle], [Pretorian], [Doomer] or [Interceptor]. 
    <p />
    The [CombatUnits] with [MovDiagonal] can be stuck without any way to escape if they have enemy [CombatUnits]
    on all the possible movement squares. A unit can only attack to the front, so they become completely 
    vulnerable.
    <p />
    The following example shows a [DiagonalTrap] on four corners:

    <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap2.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example" />

    And this example shows a [DiagonalTrap] on the extremity of the [GameBoard]:
    
    <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap1.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example" />

  You should be very careful when  moving your [CombatUnits] with [MovDiagonal] to an extremity of the
  [GameBoard]. Not only do they loose 50% mobility, they also become very much open to a [DiagonalTrap].

  <h2>How to fight the Diagonal Trap?</h2>
  The best way to fight it is just to avoid completely the enemy's trap. However, if you opponent manages
  to apply the trap, the only way to escape is using other [CombatUnits] to destroy the ones that
  form the trap.
    </div></lang>
		<lang key="es"><h1>Trampa Diagonal</h1><div class="content">
 
  La [DiagonalTrap] es una táctica que permite aproveitar las limitaciones de movimiento de todas las unidades con
  [MovDiagonal], como por ejemplo: [Eagle], [Pretorian], [Doomer] o [Interceptor]. Muchos jugadores llaman cariñosamente
  a esta táctica: <i>prisión de vientre</i>.
  <p />
  Las [CombatUnits] con [MovDiagonal] pueden quedar presas sin cualquier forma de escape si tuvieran 
  [CombatUnits] adversárias en todas las cuadrículas para donde se pueden mover. Como solo atacan hacia adelante, quedan
  completamente vulnerables.
  <p />
  El siguiente ejemplo muestra una [DiagonalTrap] en las cuatro esquinas:

  <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap2.png" alt="Exemplo de Armadilha Diagonal" />

  Y este ejemplo muestra una [DiagonalTrap] en la extremidad del [GameBoard]:

  <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap1.png" alt="Exemplo de Armadilha Diagonal" />
    
    Se debe tener siempre mucho cuidado en tener [CombatUnits] con [MovDiagonal] en una extremidade de [GameBoard].
    Más allá  que pierden el 50% de mobilidad, quedan mucho mas abiertas a una [DiagonalTrap].
    
    <h2>Como combatir una Trampa Diagonal?</h2>
    La mejor forma es evitar por completo caer en la [DiagonalTrap]. A pesar de esto , si el adversário consigue aplicar 
    la Trampa, la única forma es con outras [CombatUnits] destruir las unidades que compnen la Trampa.
  </div></lang>
		<lang key="fr"><h1>Piège Diagonal</h1><div class="content">
    La [DiagonalTrap] est une tactique dont le but est de prendre avantage des limitations des unités pouvant seulement se déplacer à la diagonale. [MovDiagonal] Par exemple, le [Eagle], le [Pretorian], le [Doomer] et l'[Interceptor]. 
    <p />
    Les [CombatUnits] avec [MovDiagonal] peuvent être pris au piège sans pouvoir s'échapper si il y a des [CombatUnits] adverses sur chacun des coins par rapport à cet unité. can be stuck without any way to escape if they have enemy [CombatUnits]
 Une unité ne peut pas attaquer directement les cases diagonales et devient donc complètement vulnérable.
    <p />
    Voici un exemple montrant une [DiagonalTrap] sur les 4 coins:

    <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap2.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example" />

    Et cet exemple montre une [DiagonalTrap] sur une extremité du [GameBoard]:
    
    <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap1.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example" />

  Vous devriez faire très attention lorsque vous déplacez des [CombatUnits] avec [MovDiagonal] à l'extrêmité du
  [GameBoard]. Non seulement cette unité perd 50% de sa mobilité, elle risque aussi de tomber plus facilement dans une [DiagonalTrap].

  <h2>Comment combattre un piège diagonal?</h2>
  La meilleura façon de combattre cette tactique est simplement d'éviter le piège de l'adversaire. Si l'ennemi réussit tout de même à vous attirer dans son piège, la seule façon de sauver l'unité victime est d'utiliser d'autres [CombatUnits] pour détruire celle qui forment la trappe.
    </div></lang>
		<lang key="hr"><h1>Dijagonalna Zamka</h1><div class="content">
[DiagonalTrap] je taktika koja cilja da iskotristi limite pokreta [MovDiagonal] jedinca, na primjer: [Eagle], [Pretorian], [Doomer] or [Interceptor]. 
<p />
[CombatUnits] sa [MovDiagonal] mogu zapeti bez bilo kakvog načina da pobjegnu ako imaju naprijateljske [CombatUnits] na svim mogućim kvadratima na koje se mogu pomaknuti. Jedinica može napadati samo naprijed, pa zbog toga postaje kompletno ranjiva. 
<p />
Sljedeći primjer pokazuje [DiagonalTrap] u četiri kuta:

<img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap2.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example" />


A ovaj primjer pokazuje [DiagonalTrap] na rubu [GameBoard]:

<img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap1.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example" />

Trebali biste biti jako oprezni kada mičete [CombatUnits] sa [MovDiagonal] na rub [GameBoard]. Ne samo da izgube 50% mobilnosti, već postaju i laka meta za [DiagonalTrap].

<h2>Kako se boriti protiv Dijagonalne Zamke</h2>
Najbolji način da se bori protiv nje je da se u potpunosti izbjegne protivnikova zamka. Međutim, ako protivnik uspije primjeniti zamku, jedini način da se pobjegne iz nje je korištenje drugih [CombatUnits] da unište one koje formiraju zamku.
</div></lang>
		<lang key="it"><h1>Trappola Diagonale</h1><div class="content">
    La [DiagonalTrap] è una tattica che mira ad avantaggiarsi delle limitazioni di movimento delle unità [MovDiagonal], come ad esempio: [Eagle], [Pretorian], [Doomer] o [Interceptor]. 
    <p>
    Le [CombatUnits] con [MovDiagonal] possono essere bloccate senza via di fuga se hanno  [CombatUnits] nemiche in ogni possibile casella di movimento. Una unità può attaccare solo di fronte a se, quindi diventa completamente vulnerabile.
    </p><p>
    Il seguente esempio mostra una [DiagonalTrap] su quattro angoli:

    <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap2.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example" />

    E questo mostra una [DiagonalTrap] sul lato della [GameBoard]:
    
    <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap1.png" alt="Diagonal Trap Example" />

  Devi essere molto attento quando muovi le tue [CombatUnits] con [MovDiagonal] a una estremità della [GameBoard]. Non solo perdono il 50% della mobilità, ma diventano aperte ad attacchi di tipo [DiagonalTrap].

  </p><h2>Come si contrasta la Trappola Diagonale?</h2>
  Il modo migliore di contrastarla è evitarla completamente. Ad ogni modo se il tuo avversario riesce a intrappolarti, l'unico modo di scappare è usando altre [CombatUnits] per distruggere quelle che formano la trappola.
    </div></lang>
		<lang key="pt"><h1>Armadilha Diagonal</h1><div class="content">
  A [DiagonalTrap] é uma táctica que visa aproveitar as limitações de movimento de todas as unidades com
  [MovDiagonal], como por exemplo: [Eagle], [Pretorian], [Doomer] ou [Interceptor]. Muitos jogadores chamam
  carinhosamente a esta táctica: <i>prisão de ventre</i>.
  <p />
  As [CombatUnits] com [MovDiagonal] podem ficar presas sem qualquer forma de escapar se tiverem
  [CombatUnits] adversárias em todas as quadrículas para onde se podem mover. Como só atacam em frente, ficam
  completamente vulneráveis.
  <p />
  O seguinte exemplo mostra uma [DiagonalTrap] nos quatro cantos:

  <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap2.png" alt="Exemplo de Armadilha Diagonal" />

  E este exemplo mostra uma [DiagonalTrap] na extremidade do [GameBoard]:

  <img class="block" src="/Resources/Images/DiagonalTrap1.png" alt="Exemplo de Armadilha Diagonal" />
    
    Deve-se ter sempre muito cuidado em ter [CombatUnits] com [MovDiagonal] numa extremidade do [GameBoard].
    Além de perderem 50% de mobilidade, ficam muito mais abertas a uma [DiagonalTrap].
    
    <h2>Como combater a Armadilha Diagonal?</h2>
    A melhor forma é evitar por completo cair na [DiagonalTrap]. Contudo, se o adversário conseguir aplicar 
    a armadilha, a única forma é com outras [CombatUnits] destruir as unidades que compõem a armadilha.
  </div></lang>
		<lang key="tr"></lang>
	</entry>

</resources>
